James House

Yorba Linda, CA 92886 | (714) 322-5296 | Housejames18@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Recent graduate from the University of California, Riverside with a Bachelor of Arts degree in History. Interested in exploring a career beyond Humanities in Information Technology. A self-taught technical troubleshooter with seven years of experience constructing personal computers. Recently completed Google's technical support fundamentals certificate and am not in the process of doing the following four courses and looking to complete the CompTIA certificates.

EDUCATION

University of California Riverside

Riverside, CA

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) History – U.S. History

Sept 2020 - June 2022

• GPA: 3.52

• Dean's List: Sept 2020 – June 2022

• Activities: American Marketing Association

Irvine Valley College

Irvine, CA

Associate in Arts (AA) Humanities and Languages | Liberal Studies: Teacher Education (2020)

Aug 2018 - May 2020

Associate in Arts (AA) Liberal Studies | Liberal Studies: Teacher Education (2020)

EXPERIENCE

Bodhi Leaf Coffee Traders

Anaheim Hills, CA

October 2019 - Present

Barista Shift Lead
 Head the barista team, delegating responsibilities amongst the employees in order to maintain quality work.

- Integrating daily tasks into the Cafe routine to ensure cleanliness and effectiveness of the time and workspace.
- Collaborate with other Shift leads and management to serve the highest quality product and advocate for the concerns and suggestions of my fellow teammates
- Deliver exceptional customer service skills and mediate intense customer service issues throughout the store
- Experienced in troubleshooting problems such as internet going down or POS system going down.

McDonald's Anaheim Hills, CA

NICDONAIG'SCrew Member

J

June 2017 - October 2019

• Interacted with customers in a vibrant fashion to create a fun environment.

Building Customized PCs

Anaheim Hills, CA

(Independently)

December 2015 - Present

- Self-taught PC builder who engineers customizable PC computers for customers throughout my community based on preferences and everyday use
- Assess all potential parts and supplies needed to assemble the perfect PC and calculate total costs of parts to account for client's budgets while also providing a high-quality computer
- Stay up to date with new, high-quality computer parts to be well informed about all of the potential parts to use for future projects

CERTIFICATIONS

Google IT Support Professional Certificate

Yorba Linda, CA

Completed the Support Fundamentals course in two weeks

August 2022

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Constructed over ten personal computers fit to the needs desired.
- Proficient in Google and Microsoft Applications
- Exceptional communicator and problem solver
- Accomplished in customer service and customer mediation
- Efficient at problem-solving and troubleshooting technical issues